<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tutores>

      <tutor id="tutorInicio" titulo="Register a catalog" pbS="yes(y)" pbN="" sizeHeight ="500">
	<html><body>
    	<p>
        	The behavioral catalog module is used to register persistent catalogs of behaviors, that can be recalled and used later in categorical behavioral transcription.
    	</p>

    	<h2>NEXT</h2>
    	<p>
        	Pres “yes” to start entering your behavioral categories or items.
    	</p>

	</body></html></tutor>


   <tutor id="tutorPrenchaCampos" titulo="Fill all the fields and press" pbS="yes(y)" pbN="" sizeHeight ="530">
	<html><body>

<p>
	Preencha os campos obrigatórios:
</p>
	<p>
    	<ul>
      	<li><font color="red">User ID: </font>your name  </li>
      	<li><font color="red">Lab info: </font>the name of your lab or unit o</li>
    	</ul>
	</p>

	<h2> <font color="red">IMPORTANT! </font></h2>
	<p>
    	Use at least 8 characters including letters and numbers, but no special characters 	</p>
	<h2> Next</h2>
	<p>
    	Press <font color="red"> save</font>.
	</p>
	</body></html></tutor>
	
	
	<tutor id="tutorPrenchaCamposNameCodeDescription" titulo="Add a behavior" pbS="yes(y)" pbN="" sizeHeight ="600">
	<html><body>
    	<p>
        	Fill the fields :
    	</p>
	<p>
    	<ul>
      	<li><font color="red"> Name </font> With the name of the behavior (any number of characters, letters and numbers, without special characters).</li>
      	<li><font color="red"> Shortcut</font> With an alphanumeric code (maximum of 3 letters and/or numbers, UTF-coded) . </li>
      	<li><font color="red"> Description </font> With a textual, operational description of this behavior (any number of characters, letters and numbers, without special characters) </li>
    	</ul>
	</p>

	<h2> <font color="red">WARNING! </font></h2>
	<p>
    	Todos os campos a não ser o campo shortcut, podem ser preenchidos por quantidades de caracteres maior do que 1 desde que sejam da codificação UTF-8 e não contenha caracteres especiais (e.g., ãçéó)
	</p>
	
	<h2> NEXT</h2>
	<p>
     	Press <font color="red"> add to catalog </font> to add a behavior.
	</p>
	</body></html></tutor>




    <tutor id="tutoCatalogUnits" titulo="Behavior catalog units table" pbS="ok(f1)" pbN="" sizeHeight ="400">
    <html><body>

        Nessa tabela, são apresentadas as categorias criadas para o novo catálogo. Cada linha corresponde a uma categoria, sendo a primeira coluna referente ao nome dessa categoria e a segunda referente ao seu código.

    </body></html></tutor>


   <tutor id="tutoCatalogUnits" titulo="Behaviors in the catalog" pbS="ok(f1)" pbN="" sizeHeight ="400">
	<html><body>

    	This table shows all the behaviors inserted in the catalog. 

	</body></html></tutor>



    <tutor id="tutorSalva" titulo="Save the catalog" pbS="yes(y)" pbN="" sizeHeight ="300">
	<html><body>
    	<p>
         	Press <font color="red"> Save the catalog </font> to save and close the window.
    	</p>
	</body></html></tutor>
	
	<tutor id="tutorDele" titulo="Delete behaviors" pbS="ok(f1)" pbN="" sizeHeight ="400">
	<html><body>

    	<p>
        	Siga os passos:
    	</p>
    	<p>

        	<ul>
          	<li><font color="red"> Passo 1 </font> Select a behavior to be deleted by pressing in the corresponding line in the table of behaviors</li>
          	<li><font color="red"> Passo 2 </font> Press Delete selected behavior </li>
        	</ul>
    	</p>

    	<p>
        	Ao seguir esses passos você irá excluir o item selecionado do catálogo.
    	</p>
	</body></html></tutor>







</tutores>
